<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bogdan Toader</title>
    <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bogdan Toader</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://bogdantoader.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Preprints: B. Toader, J. Boulanger, Y. Korolev, M. O. Lenz, J. Manton, C.-B. Schönlieb, L. Mureşan Image reconstruction in light-sheet microscopy: spatially varying deconvolution and mixed noise 2021 S. Chrétien, A. Thompson, B. Toader The dual approach to non-negative super-resolution: perturbation analysis 2020 Journal articles and conference proceedings: A. Eftekhari, J. Tanner, A. Thompson, B. Toader and H. Tyagi Sparse non-negative super-resolution --- simplified and stabilised Applied and Computational Harmonic Analysis, 2019 S.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Stability of non-negative super-resolution Collaborators: Dr Armin Eftekhari, Prof Jared Tanner, Dr Andrew Thompson, Dr Hemant Tyagi
The convolution of a discrete measure, $x=\sum_{i=1}^ka_i\delta_{t_i}$, with a local window function, $\phi(s-t)$, is a common model for a measurement device whose resolution is substantially lower than that of the objects being observed. Super-resolution concerns localising the point sources $\{a_i,t_i\}_{i=1}^k$ with an accuracy beyond the essential support of $\phi(s-t)$, typically from $m$ samples $y(s_j)=\sum_{i=1}^k a_i\phi(s_j-t_i)+\eta_j$, where $\eta_j$ indicates an inexactness in the sample value.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2021 Focus on Microscopy 2021 Online Conference, online &amp;ndash; oral presentation 2020 Virtual 12th Light Sheet Fluorescence Microscopy Conference 2020, online &amp;ndash; oral presentation
SIAM Conference on Imaging Science (IS20), online &amp;ndash; poster presentation
Quantitative BioImaging Conference (QBI 2020), Oxford, UK &amp;ndash; poster presentation
2019 Data Study Group, Alan Turing Institute, London, UK Implemented deep learning based solution for image segmentation applied to brighfield microscopy data, problem proposed by Dstl</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>UK Graduate Modelling Camp - Mentor Newton Gateway to Mathematics, 2021, Cambridge
Numerical Analysis - Supervisions Michaelmas and Lent terms 2020, University of Cambridge
Integer Programming - TA Michaelmas term 2016, 2017, University of Oxford
Continuous Optimisation - TA Hilary term 2017, 2018, University of Oxford
Computational Mathematics - Demonstrator Michaelmas term 2016, Hilary term 2017, University of Oxford</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
