<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Bogdan Toader</title>
    <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Bogdan Toader</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://bogdantoader.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/publications/</guid>
      <description>Academic articles An image processing pipeline for electron cryo-tomography in RELION-5 A. Burt, B. Toader, R. Warshamanage, A. von Kügelgen, E. Pyle, J. Zivanov, D. Kimanius, T.A.M. Bharat, S.H.W. Scheres bioRxiv: https://doi.org/10.1101/2024.04.26.591129, 2024 Efficient high-resolution refinement in cryo-EM with stochastic gradient descent B. Toader, M. A. Brubaker, R. R. Lederman arXiv:2311.16100, 2023 On Manifold Learning in Plato&#39;s Cave: Remarks on Manifold Learning and Physical Phenomena R. R. Lederman, B. Toader International Conference on Sampling Theory and Applications (SampTA), 2023 Methods for Cryo-EM Single Particle Reconstruction of Macromolecules Having Continuous Heterogeneity B.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/research/</guid>
      <description>Stability of non-negative super-resolution Collaborators: Dr Armin Eftekhari, Prof Jared Tanner, Dr Andrew Thompson, Dr Hemant Tyagi&#xA;The convolution of a discrete measure, $x=\sum_{i=1}^ka_i\delta_{t_i}$, with a local window function, $\phi(s-t)$, is a common model for a measurement device whose resolution is substantially lower than that of the objects being observed. Super-resolution concerns localising the point sources $\{a_i,t_i\}_{i=1}^k$ with an accuracy beyond the essential support of $\phi(s-t)$, typically from $m$ samples $y(s_j)=\sum_{i=1}^k a_i\phi(s_j-t_i)+\eta_j$, where $\eta_j$ indicates an inexactness in the sample value.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/talks/</guid>
      <description>2023 International Conference on Sampling Theory and Applications (SampTA 2023), Yale University, US &amp;ndash; Oral presentation&#xA;Flatiron Institute CryoEM Summer Workshop, New York, US &amp;ndash; Poster presentation&#xA;SIAM Conference on Computational Science and Engineering (CSE23), Amsterdam, The Netherlands – Mini-symposium presentation&#xA;2022 IPAM Seminar, UCLA, US &amp;ndash; Oral presentation&#xA;SIAM Conference on Mathematics of Data Science (MDS22), San Diego, US &amp;ndash; Poster presentation&#xA;PIMS Workshop on Mathematical and Computational Challenges in Cryo-EM, Vancouver, Canada &amp;ndash; Oral presentation</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://bogdantoader.github.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://bogdantoader.github.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>UK Graduate Modelling Camp - Mentor Newton Gateway to Mathematics, 2021, Cambridge&#xA;Numerical Analysis - Supervisions Michaelmas and Lent terms 2020, University of Cambridge&#xA;Integer Programming - TA Michaelmas term 2016, 2017, University of Oxford&#xA;Continuous Optimisation - TA Hilary term 2017, 2018, University of Oxford&#xA;Computational Mathematics - Demonstrator Michaelmas term 2016, Hilary term 2017, University of Oxford</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
